- Get back! No New Interest allowed here!
- Aye, if your ribbons aren't blue, you're
cue-2
not coming through!
This election is an outrage! I've fought my
cue-3
way past those Old Interest bludgeons, and
now they've set their lawyer on me!
cue-4
Trying to pretend I'm not eligible to
vote!
cue-5
Why don't you do something about
your friends with bludgeons down there?! The
cue-6
ones blocking anyone who wants to vote
New Interest from getting to the polling
cue-7
place?! That's what's against the law!
But I won't be intimidated. My vote's my
cue-8
right, and it's as good as anyone else's.
Far better than those who have been
cue-9
bought. Unbribed, I vote, and that's my
pride. I always choose the honest
cue-10
side.